const BrainrotQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        image: '/src/assets/images/1.webp',
        question: 'Who is this?',
        options: ['Trippi Troppi', 'Tralalero Tralala', 'Lirilì Larilà', 'Bobrito Bandito'],
        answer: 'Tralalero Tralala'
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        image: '/src/assets/images/2.webp',
        question: 'Which one is shown?',
        options: ['Trippi Troppi', 'Chimpanzini Bananini', 'Girafa Celestre', 'Bombardiro Crocodilo'],
        answer: 'Trippi Troppi'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        image: '/src/assets/images/3.webp',
        question: 'Name this one!',
        options: ['Tralalero Tralala', 'Capuccino Assassino', 'Tung Tung Tung Sahur', 'Trulimero Trulicina'],
        answer: 'Tung Tung Tung Sahur'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        image: '/src/assets/images/4.webp',
        question: 'Which character is this?',
        options: ['Bobrito Bandito', 'Bombombini Gusini', 'Frigo Camelo', 'Chimpanzini Bananini'],
        answer: 'Chimpanzini Bananini'
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        image: '/src/assets/images/5.webp',
        question: 'Who is this?',
        options: ['Bombombini Gusini', 'Bombardiro Crocodilo', 'Brr Brr Patapim', 'Bobrito Bandito'],
        answer: 'Bombardiro Crocodilo'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        image: '/src/assets/images/6.webp',
        question: 'Which character is this?',
        options: ['Frigo Camelo', 'Pot Hotspot', 'Trulimero Trulicina', 'Ballerina Cappucina'],
        answer: 'Ballerina Cappucina'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        image: '/src/assets/images/7.webp',
        question: 'Name this one!',
        options: ['Garamaraman dan Madudungdung', 'Bombombini Gusini', 'Brri Brri Bicus Dicus Bombicus', 'Blueberrinni Octopussini'],
        answer: 'Bombombini Gusini'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        image: '/src/assets/images/8.webp',
        question: 'Which one is shown?',
        options: ['Girafa Celestre', 'Burbaloni Lulilolli', 'Lirilì Larilà', 'Abonono Schimpazinono'],
        answer: 'Lirilì Larilà'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        image: '/src/assets/images/9.webp',
        question: 'Which character is this?',
        options: ['Capuccino Assassino', 'Espressona Signora', 'Chef Crabracadabra', 'Il Cacto Hipopotamo'],
        answer: 'Capuccino Assassino'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        image: '/src/assets/images/10.webp',
        question: 'Who is this?',
        options: ['Tigrrullini Watermellini', 'Graipussi Medussi', 'Orangutini Ananasini', 'Fruli Frula'],
        answer: 'Orangutini Ananasini'
    }
];

export default BrainrotQuestions